[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Poisoning by this substance is often referred to as painters colic.", "correct_answer": "Lead", "incorrect_answers": ["Thallium", "Barium", "Chromium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It is the only continent that does not have land areas below sea level.", "correct_answer": "Antarctica", "incorrect_answers": ["Australia", "South America", "Arctica"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What color is the head of the South American stork Jabiru, whose body is predominantly white?", "correct_answer": "Black", "incorrect_answers": ["Purple", "Green", "Red"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The animals from which group are often called sea cows?", "correct_answer": "Sirenia", "incorrect_answers": ["Enhydra", "Odobenidae", "Otariidae"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Theres Something About Mary what actor plays the character who turns out to be Woogie?", "correct_answer": "Chris Elliott", "incorrect_answers": ["Matt Dillon", "Keith David", "Harland Williams"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Venus travels around the Sun at an average distance of how many miles?", "correct_answer": "67 million miles", "incorrect_answers": ["120 million miles", "1.2 billion miles", "38 million miles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Josef von Sternberg made this lady a star when he cast her as Lola-Lola in The Blue Angel.\nWho sang Men cluster to me like moths to a flame. And if they get burned, I know Im not to blame?", "correct_answer": "Marlene Dietrich", "incorrect_answers": ["Theda Bara", "Clara Bow", "Mary Pickford"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is a variety of ring-shaped pasta, typically stuffed with a mix of meat and usually served in broth, with cream, or sometimes with a rag\u00f9. It originated in the Italian region of Emilia.", "correct_answer": "tortellini", "incorrect_answers": ["cannelloni", "ravioli", "gnocchi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many hours approximately does an eggshell formation take in an average laying hen?", "correct_answer": "About 20 hours", "incorrect_answers": ["About 48 hours", "About 5 hours", "Less than 2 hours"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "From what movie directed by Stanley Kubrick is the quote Heres Johnny!?", "correct_answer": "The Shining", "incorrect_answers": ["2001: A Space Odyssey", "Dr. Strangelove or: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love the Bomb", "Lolita"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During the years of the Civil War molasses was made using maple syrup because it did not require slave labor.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At what time of the day are Tasmanian devils most active?", "correct_answer": "At night", "incorrect_answers": ["Early morning", "At noon", "During the daytime"]}]